Hamse Mare

Phone: (780)-716-6256, E-Mail: hamse@ualberta.ca

Summary Highlights

I am a Second year Computing Science Major with a Specialization in Software Practice. I am effective at completing difficult projects and tasks on schedule. Also, I am very dependable, hard working, and an excellent team player. I Thrive in a fast-paced environment and I consistently follow through with all orders and instructions. Lastly, I work really well in a team setting.

Reference

• Victor Francoeur : (780)-604-5858

Highlights

- Exceptional problem solver
- Great team player / Co-worker Stemming from work
- · experience Excellent leadership qualities
- Can execute tasks under pressure
- Learn very quickly from mistakes
- · I can become an asset to this company

Accomplishments

- Demonstrated strong communication skills through years of experience in customer service related positions
- Attend University of Alberta
- Received the Rutherford Scholarship 2016
- · Active Member in community, Volunteering

Projects To Date

- UberFitness (Workout Tracker, currently in the works)
- Many smaller scale projects, and assignments

Education

University of Alberta

Sept 2016 - Present

- o BSc With Specialization Computing Science Software Practice
- o 3.4 GPA (Most Recent Year)
- Software Engineering (Python, C)
- o Computer System Architecture courses
- o Finite Mathematics
- o Microsoft Word, Outlook, PowerPoint, Excel
- o Linux, OS X, Ubuntu
- o Python, C, C++
- Basic Knowledge (HTML, CSS, JavaScript)

Harry Ainlay High School

Sept 2013 - Sept 2016

- o 84% Average
- o Graduated with Honors
- Attended seminar on Harassment, Bullying and Cyber-Intimidation in School
- o Attended a Learning-Disabilities seminar and Violence-in-School seminar

Experience

The Brick May 2017 - Sept 2017

- o Responsible for the delivery of appliances to customers
- Feedback from superiors consistently positive

Save On Foods

Jul 2014 - Jan 2017

- Responsible for the deliveries to the store.
- o Responsible for the organization of the store
- o Trained new staff regulary.

Staples Nov 2013 - Aug 2014

- Responsible for the training of new staff. Depature due to
- movement of permanent residence

Habitat For Humanity

Jul 2013 - Aug 2013

- Volunteered for the summer of 2013
- Assisted in the development of homes to local families

McDonalds Sept 2012 - Nov 2013

- Server Customers in a timely manner Assisted in
- the training of new crew workers Employee of the
- month on two occasions Depature due to new
- oppurtunities

Personal Information

• Place of Birth: Ottawa, Ontario

• Date of Birth: 24th of June, 1998

• Present Resident: Edmonton, Alberta

• Sex: Male

Hobbies: Weightlifting, International Travel

Contact

• Phone: (780)-705-5363

(780)-716-6256

• E-mail: hamse@ualberta.ca